zerply.com 2016-06-27

# Privacy Policy - Zerply

## Privacy Policy

### ZERPLY, INC.

Zerply, Inc. (“Zerply”) is committed to protecting your privacy. Please take a moment to read and learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the Zerply website (the “Website”), submitting information or using any of our services (the “Zerply Service”), or creating an account to use the Zerply Services (a “Zerply Account”), you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

**What is Covered in This Privacy Policy?**

This Privacy Policy covers Zerply's treatment of personally identifiable information (collectively with “Submitted Information” (as defined herein), the "Personal Information") that Zerply gathers when you are accessing the Website and when you use the Zerply Service or register for a Zerply Account. Furthermore, this Privacy Policy covers Zerply's treatment of any Personal Information that Zerply's business partners share with Zerply. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Zerply does not own or control, or to individuals that Zerply does not employ or manage.

**What Personal Information is Collected by Zerply?**

The types of Personal Information collected may include your full name, website URL, e-mail address, blog or other personal website URL, your nickname or screenname, and any other information that would allow Zerply to identify you or contact you if needed.

In addition to the Personal Information mentioned, we may ask you to provide certain other information such as general demographic information, including age, gender, ZIP code, preferences, and interests. The information we gather from our users enables us to personalize and improve the Zerply Service. 

We may receive and store any information you enter on the Website or provide to us in any other way. The Personal Information you provide may be used for providing attribution to comments you post, to operate and improve the Website, and to better deliver the Zerply Service. 

**Information from Social Networking Websites**

By registering for a Zerply Account, you may have the option to sign in using third party social networking websites (collectively, the “Social Networks”), such as Facebook and LinkedIn. If you choose to sign in through these Social Networks, we use the information you have already provided to such Social Networks in registering for an account with such Social Networks and which you have allowed such Social Networks to share with Zerply, including, but not limited to, your first name, your user profile picture, your friends and contacts list, pages your gender, and the networks to which you belong (collectively, your “Submitted Information”). 

You expressly authorize us to collect and use your Submitted Information in connection with your use of the Zerply Services You further acknowledge and agree that Zerply may, but is not obligated to, maintain copies of your Submitted Information indefinitely, or delete any or all Submitted Information, at our sole discretion.

We advise you to carefully read to the terms of use and privacy policies of Social Networks (collectively, the “SNW Policies”). It is your responsibility to read and accept the respective SNW Policies prior to signing into your Zerply Account through such Social Networks.

**Information Collected Automatically**

We may receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with the Website and/or Zerply Service. Zerply may choose to automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested.

Zerply uses "cookies" to collect non-personal data and information. Cookies are small text files a website uses to recognize repeat users, and is typically placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. The way cookies function is by assigning a number to the user that has no meaning outside of the assigning website.

You should be aware that Zerply cannot control the use of cookies (or the resulting information) by Zerply's third-party partners or advertisers. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of the Website and Zerply Service that depend on cookies.

**Sharing of Personal Information**

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, your personal information will be used only by Zerply and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates, and your personal information will not be disclosed to any other third party without your consent. 

Zerply occasionally hires other companies to provide limited administrative and communication services on our behalf, such as hosting websites, the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, or performing statistical analysis of the Services. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only such personal information as necessary for them to deliver the service. Those companies are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes.

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if Zerply, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Zerply may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

Pursuant to the license granted by you to Zerply under the Terms of Use, which can be accessed at zerply.com/about/terms, Zerply has the right to use any ideas, information, statements, files, photos, images, or links you post to the Zerply site. You hereby consent to Zerply’s disclosure and/or sublicense of such content by Zerply to third parties, including the use and disclosure by Zerply and any third party of your personal information for purposes of attributing such content to you.

Zerply may access and/or disclose personal information about you or your account without your prior consent if Zerply has a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (i) comply with legal process or other legal requirements of any governmental authority; (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of Zerply (including the enforcement of our agreements); (iii) enforce the Terms of Use, which can be accessed at [zerply.com/about/terms](http://zerply.com/about/terms) (v) operate or conduct maintenance and repair of the Services or equipment as authorized by law; or (vi) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Zerply Services or members of the public.

**Security and Protection of Personal Information**

We maintain reasonable standards of security and confidentiality and store Personal Information collected in a database. However, while we employ reasonable standards of security, no security system is impenetrable. For most internet sites, it is possible that third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions you submit. As such, Zerply cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won’t be intercepted while being transmitted to Zerply over the internet. We recommend that you do not disclose your password or confirmation number (as applicable) to anyone.

**E-mail Communications**

Upon registration for events and/or services provided by Zerply, we may send you daily or weekly e-mails. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please notify us by e-mail at [unsubscribe@zerply.com](mailto:unsubscribe@zerply.com) and include sufficient information for us to identify your account, including your name, email address and the specifics of your request. However, after you unsubscribe to cease receiving e-mails, Zerply may still contact you via e-mail for administrative or informational purposes, including messages regarding the administration of your account and/or any services or events to which you have registered.

**Advertisements Displayed by Third Parties**

Zerply may allow third-party ad serving companies, including ad networks, to display advertisements on the Website. Ad serving companies may place a persistent cookie on your computer in order to recognize your computer each time they display an online advertisement to you, and as such, they may be able to compile information over time about whether you reviewed or clicked on advertisements they display. These companies may use this information to display targeted advertisements and may associate this information with your subsequent visits, purchases or other activities on participating advertisers’ websites. Zerply has no access to or control over cookies of these links to other websites and organizations, nor does Zerply have control over or access to cookies by Zerply’s third-party partners or advertisers. This Privacy Policy does not cover any use of Personal Information that a third-party advertiser or ad server may collect from you.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Zerply retains the discretion to amend or modify this Privacy Policy from time to time, in its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. If we make changes in the way we use your Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Website, and such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting. You agree to review this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes. Your continued access or use of the Website and/or the Zerply Service shall be deemed your conclusive acceptance of any amendments and/or modifications.

**Questions or Comments Regarding this Privacy Policy**

Zerply welcomes any questions or comments you may have regarding this Privacy Policy or if you do not understand any information about how we collect, maintain, use, or share your Personal Information. Any such questions or comments should be submitted via email to privacy@zerply.com We will make every effort to resolve or answer your concern.

**Modifications of this Privacy Notice**

ZERPLY MAY MODIFY THIS PRIVACY NOTICE AT ANY TIME, IN ZERPLY’S SOLE DISCRETION, AND SUCH MODIFICATION SHALL BE EFFECTIVE IMMEDIATELY UPON EITHER POSTING OF THE MODIFIED PRIVACY NOTICE ON THE WEBSITE OR NOTIFYING YOU. YOU AGREE TO REVIEW THIS PRIVACY NOTICE PERIODICALLY TO ENSURE THAT YOU ARE AWARE OF ANY MODIFICATIONS. YOUR CONTINUED ACCESS OR USE OF THE WEBSITE AND/OR THE SOFTWARE SHALL BE DEEMED YOUR CONCLUSIVE ACCEPTANCE OF THE MODIFIED PRIVACY NOTICE.

**Effective Date of this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 19, 2015.
